cuckolds.co.uk 2013-12-14

# Privacy Policy - Cuckolds.co.uk

This website is for over 18 year olds only. If you are not 18 years or older then [click here](https://www.google.co.uk/)

We need to put cookies on your computer. If you want to know more about what the cookies will be used for see our cookie & privacy notice [here](http://www.cuckolds.co.uk/forums/privacypolicy/). By using the site you accept that we will put cookies on your computer.

**We have over 122,000 Hotwives, Bulls & Cucks waiting to meet you today! **

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.

**Cookies**

This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties. 

  1.  
  2. [Privacy Policy](http://www.cuckolds.co.uk/forums/privacypolicy/)
  3. [Site Usage Terms And Conditions -----](http://www.cuckolds.co.uk/forums/index.php?app=forums&module=extras&section=boardrules) ·
